This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Bucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, Impel Down.
While Buggy and Mr. Three escaped from level four,
Luffy, who had been poisoned by Warden Magellan,
was whisked off to a mysterious haven for prisoners known as New Karma Land.
There, he received treatment from its leader, Ivankov.
I know what's going on in the world right now.
There's been a shift in the tide and big changes are coming.
The Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates are taking center stage.
Even so, the big man's still waiting things out.
I'm of course referring to my comrade,
the leader of all revolutionaries in the world.
You may know him as Dragon!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
What?
Your dear Papa.
And I never knew.
Godness!
After hearing that Luffy is Dragon's son,
Ivankov decided to join him in his efforts to rescue Ace.
The fever card was pointing down,
which means he's still here and still alive, thank goodness.
This is it, Quircus D. Ace.
You're going to be transferred to Marine Port.
Upon your arrival there,
you will be taken to the execution grounds.
Ace's convoy begins.
Battle on the lowest floor, level six.
Ace!
Hurry up!
Don't let them get past us!
Ready?
Move it, I'm in a hurry!
Aim!
Now gum gum!
Pistol!
Whoa!
Oh, yeah?
How do you like this?
What a bothersome little trap!
There!
Wee!
Yee-haw!
We're short on time.
Huh?
Oh, yes, I'm sorry.
Who are you people?
How did you-
Hello there.
I'm going to need to borrow you for a moment.
No, wait!
Stop it!
It won't hurt, I promise.
Let me go!
Almost there.
Let's just hope we're not too late.
All right, guys.
Don't let him through!
You don't have time for this!
Now gum gum!
Ricochet!
The trap didn't work, sir.
And all the jailers are out cold.
Straw Hat Luffy, Ivankov Queen of the Queers, and Inazuma the Revolutionary.
All three criminals are now entering level six.
What are we going to do?
Hey!
We made it.
This is level six.
It's known as the Eternal Hell, where only the most legendary of criminals have been held.
The Eternal Hell, where are you?
Hey Ace! Where are you?
It's your brother!
I'm here to save you!
Can you hear me?
Ace!
The direct approach is a no-no.
That's where you come in, sweetie
Mind telling us where he is
Uh-uh, no way
Whatever shall I do
We need to be more open with each other and with ourselves
What are you doing?
Emporio
Female hormone
Is this me?
Whoa, he turned into a girl
It's the you you were always afraid to be
Look
I'm
Beautiful
You've been reborn, my dear
You're no longer a jailer
You're a newcomer now
Thank you
What have I been doing all of these years?
My gosh, I don't know how I can ever repay you, Eva
Oh, it's nothing, don't mention it
Ah, there is one thing
Where is Ace?
Down that way
Ace!
This one?
He's gone
Are you absolutely certain that this is the right cell?
Yes, I promise you
He, he was just here, I swear
We're a bit late, it seems
A straw hat
Then it's him
It must be
She said
That my brother is here
She was telling the truth
I never thought anyone could penetrate this fortress
Let alone make it all the way to level six
You there
You're straw hat, aren't you?
Yeah
You're a moment late
He was here
They took him to the elevator for the prison transfer
Go
There's still a chance you can catch them
Thanks, but who are you?
My goodness
It's you
My goodness, it's you
Alright, let's move
Thanks for the help
Whoever you are
Who is this boy?
To brave the impossible
To accomplish the inconceivable
And to charge into yet another struggle
More hopeless than the last
And Ace knew
My brother really would break into here
He does stupid things without thinking all the time
Since we were kids
He's always been reckless
And made me worry about him
That idiot
They took that elevator to the upper floor
Let's go
Thankfully, they've left the gate open
Nice
Seems the operation system is locked up
It won't budge
That sucks
Alright, we'll just have to climb up
There's no other way
Do it
Sir
Oh, man
That was close
Ah, I see
They can't let things be convenient for us
Now, can they?
We'll just have to find ourselves another way
They're watching us
Let's go back to the stairs
Oh, yeah
Just try it
Hey, those jerks blocked the staircase
They're trying to trap us
We'll just have to break through then, won't we?
Sounds good
That's an awful lot of gas
Do you think it's deadly?
Poison gas again?
Hey, you!
Listen up!
I don't know who the hell you punks are
But if you're gonna get yourselves killed
Don't take us with you
Shut up!
Nobody cares!
Doesn't matter if it's poisonous
I gotta go!
Wait!
Well, there you have it
Sleeping gas
The boy didn't even give it a second thought
At least trying to stay alive
Get out of here already!
Move!
This is the last thing we need
I see
They're hoping to stop us without a fight
How cowardly
Vice Warden
Level 6 is now blocked off completely
The sleeping gas is highly effective
And there's nowhere to run
Just in case
Keep the guards on standby
Did you report all this to Warden Magellan?
Yes, sir
Just now
Good
That means I get to keep my job
Now to place the blame for this entire fiasco on Magellan
Then I'll become the Warden
Sir
The microphone's still on
Come on, man!
What do you know?
Straw Hat made it to level 6
Just after we left
Unfortunate timing for you
Luffy!
I wasn't in the mood for a nap
But it seems we're out of options
It's all over
The emergency sleeping gas has flooded level 6
It's only a matter of time before they catch Straw Hat
Apparently the freezing hell wasn't punishment enough for him
Since the cell you were in now has a vacancy
Straw Hat will have a taste of the torment reserved for our most heinous criminals
Luffy
No one told you to stop
Keep walking
I assure you resistance is futile
Luffy!
Your brother's a pirate
His fate was sealed the moment he stepped in this prison
Damn it, Luffy
I'd hoped Hancock was lying
But this troubles me
No matter how strong he is
He shouldn't have recovered from my poison
And so quickly
How did you do it, Straw Hat?
How did you survive?
We made it back to level 3
But that's only halfway home
Sadly, I think we moved faster on the way down
Thanks to all of those times we fell through the floor
I'm so thirsty
I think my legs are going on strike
What is it?
Let me rest for a minute, will you?
What the?
Hello
Gnocchi
You're still here?
Buckwheat noodle with bread
Eric, let us go!
Buckwheat noodle with fried tofu
Wheat flour noodle with curry
Come on, do something!
The whole floor's filling with gas
Shut up, let's go!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Well, that's one way to deal with the problem, I suppose.
I don't get it, but I like it.
Inazuma ate the snip-snip fruit, so now he's a scissor man.
He can manipulate whatever he cuts as though it's made of paper.
Really? That's cool.
Don't fall asleep! If you doze off on me, I might get drowsy!
But, I never sleep!
Stop doing that!
Good morning.
We gotta keep going up, crab guy. Thanks for blocking out the gas, but now I can't go up the stairs to get to Ace.
This is the only way to prevent the sleeping gas from filling up the room.
If you're unconscious, you can't save anybody, can you?
I'll save him whether I'm unconscious or not! I'm not gonna let him die, you understand?
Don't be ridiculous. It was a simple plan, but it defeated us nonetheless.
As much as I hate to admit it, we're trapped here on level six, at least for the time being.
Sorry, buddy. Well, this is all I can do.
At least the jerks can't watch us now.
Well, we gave it a good shot, but no time for regrets.
I'm sure that by now, they've made their way to the top floor to hand off Ace for the transfer.
Even if we could get out, we'd have quite the melange of obstacles in our way.
The Navy's convoy is quick, too. Take a look at the Viva card.
It's not pointing straight up anymore, is it?
That means that Ace has already been handed over to the Navy.
He travels around the Navy.
You're right on time.
Very good.
Impel Down hereby transfers custody of the criminal Porkus DAs to the Navy forces present today.
Here.
But it's just a scrap of paper.
Do yourself a favor and always hang on to that.
That scrap of paper will reunite us one day.
Yeah?
You don't want it?
No. I'll keep it.
I'll keep it.
Luffy.
Huh?
I'm going to Marineford!
Don't be stupid!
A massive battle is about to take place between two of the most powerful forces in the entire world!
Do you have any idea how strong Whitebeard is?
What about all the admirals, vice-admirals, and the warlords on the Navy side? Remember them?
And are you also forgetting how close to death you were after the fight with Magellan?
Do you have that many lives to spare?
What is it?!
Look, if I give up now, I'll regret it!
I know that face! I've seen it many times before!
It's the face of his father, staring at me, unflinching!
You can do as you like, but first of all, how do you propose we get off this floor?
Huh?
If you want out that bat, then set me free.
I'll make a hole in the ceiling and you'll be free to go. Sound good?
No way! They've got to hit him down here, too?!
Crocodile!
No way! They've got to hit him down here, too?! Crocodile!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! Just like old times, huh? Did you miss me?
Opie and his friends recruit Crocodile and Gene Bay, forming a plan to catch up to Ace and escape from Impel Down.
Meanwhile, Hannibal hatches a plan of his own, with the intent of intercepting them on Level 4.
With nowhere left to run, a full-scale battle breaks out inside the walls of the prison.
On the next One Piece, the ultimate team is born, shaking Impel Down! I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!